nativeremedies.com 2017-06-06

# Native Remedies Privacy Policy

### Open Policy on the Issue of Privacy

We at Native Remedies adhere to a strict professional code of ethical conduct in the handling of your personal information. Read below to review how we safeguard your relationship with us.

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### The Information We Collect 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the nativeremedies.com website whether from customers or prospects. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit Card Information

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order, to contact you with regard to your order, to respond to email inquiries, to participate in chat room discussions, or to send an email newsletter. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing Your Account on any page. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by editing it online. To protect your privacy and security, we require that you select a password, and then log on using that password to access or change your information. 

### How To Contact Us 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us using email or call customer service at +1.800.683.1235 Option 1.

### Third-Party Ads

We use a third-party service provider to service internet ads on our behalf. This provider may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. Information about your visits to this and other websites may be used for targeted advertising purposes.

This anonymous information is collected through the use of pixel tags or similar technologies which are industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process meaning that your name, address, email address or telephone number is not collected. For more information about this practice and to understand your option not to have this anonymous information used by our third party provider, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### How do you access or correct information collected?

You may limit our use of your personal information including phone number, mailing address, and e-mail address, or instruct us not to share the personal information you have provided to us with third parties by emailing us, or by contacting customer service at +1.800.683.1235.

You may easily modify my account personal information, including phone number and address, online anytime by simply logging into your account. Log in to my account to review stored information. Always remember to save your updated preferences.

You may also email write, fax or call customer service at native remedies to have any changes made to your information.

###  What information do we share with others?

Native Remedies is a subsidiary of Blyth, Inc. and as such we may share the information we collect with corporate affiliates. 

Service providers: To provide you the best possible service and products, we provide information to outside companies that help us deliver the products and services offered. For example, we may work with an outside company to manage a database of customer information or to distribute our emails.

At times we may partner with outside vendors to provide additional services or products outside those offered by NativeRemedies.com. Should you choose to accept or subscribe to offers from third parties, we may pass your relevant personal information, including name and credit card number, to the third party whose offer you have accepted. Your information will be transferred securely, and as a convenience, you will not need to re-enter your personal information. Your acceptance of a third party offer gives NativeRemedies.com implied permission to share your personal information. Your personal information will not be released without your permission, as evidenced by your acceptance or subscription to an outside third party offer.

Other companies: We do not rent or sell your e-mail address to anyone.

### How do we use Cookies?

A "cookie" is a small file stored on your computer by a web site that gathers certain information about your computer’s activity on the site (but not specifically who is using it). We use cookies to track activity and enable the interaction of our website with visitors for such things as adding items to your shopping cart and allow us to associate the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database.

Our cookies do not store any personal or financial information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies and allow you to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of the Native Remedies web site, such as the shopping basket and "My Account" will not function properly.

### Pixel Tags or Web Beacons

"Pixel tags" or "Web beacons" are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of our websites and may be placed inside emails to allow us to track certain activity. Tracked activity includes such things as being able to tell if the email was opened, how many times a recipient opened the email, whether or not they clicked a link and how many links were clicked.
